engagedforums.com 2018-12-07

# Privacy - OmniSocial Learning

**Mzinga Privacy Policy**

Mzinga provides on-demand social intelligence solutions and services in the learning, marketing, and customer experience markets. We take the private nature of your personal information very seriously, and are committed to protecting it. To that end, we’ve set up procedures to ensure that your information is handled responsibly and in accordance with applicable data protection and privacy laws.

Our privacy policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use personally identifiable information “Personal Information” that you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our websites and services (collectively, “Mzinga” or “Website”)

Mzinga complies with the E.U.-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. Mzinga has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield principals.  If there is any conflict between the terms in the privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principals, the Privacy Shield principals shall govern.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit:  [_www.privacyshield.gov_](http://www.privacyshield.gov/)

**“Personal information”** is any information that can be used to identify an individual. It does not include personal information that is encoded or anonymized, or publicly available information that has not been combined with non-public information.

This privacy policy describes what information we collect when you visit Mzinga, how we use that information, and what choices we offer you to access, update, and control it.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

We collect information two ways: Information we get from your use of a Mzinga product offering, and information you provide to us directly from the Mzinga Web Site.

**Information we get from your use of Mzinga’s product line** is primarily non-personally- identifying information of the sort that web browsers, servers, and third party services typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the time of each visit. Other non-identifying information that we might have access to includes how you use the Service (e.g. search queries), your approximate location, cookies, etc.

We collect this non-personally-identifying information in order to better understand how visitors use the Service and, where possible, to improve their experience. For instance, we log the time it takes to run database queries so that we can improve performance.

We also collect potentially personally identifying information in the form of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) accessed (which may reference the name of a board, card, or organization), and the unique identification number associated with the account. We don’t use that information to identify you, with one exception: we may discover, by reviewing log files, that a particular account is degrading the experience for all users. If this is discovered, we may look up personally identifiable information associated with that account in order to contact the account owner. We handle and disclose this information in the same way we handle other potentially personally identifying information as described below.

**Information Provided to Mzinga**

Mzinga may collect personal data from customers through a transaction or inquiry, your submission of a form, registrations, or communication to us.  Information may also be gathered from third-party sources (including without limitation, opt-in lists, publicly available data, consumer reporting agencies, other companies, and referrals) and through your activities and interactions with us.  We may combine data collected from these disparate sources unless we tell you otherwise.

The types of personal data typically collected by Mzinga may include the following, depending on your activities:

Contact information, including name, title, street address (home, work), postal code, country, telephone numbers (home, work, cell, etc.), email address (home, work), company name, and other similar information.

Personal/demographic information, e.g. gender, or level of education.

Transactional information, including products or services you inquire about, or request.

User content, including information provided when you use one of our online communities, forums or other online means of communications, and all other user submissions and content you provide.

**INFORMATION YOU CHOOSE TO DISPLAY PUBLICLY**

Some users may elect to publicly post personally identifying or sensitive information about themselves in their normal use of our communities. This could occur through use of the optional profile fields, in interactions or on public discussion boards. Information like that, which is voluntarily posted in publicly visible areas, is considered to be public, even if it would otherwise be considered to be personally identifying or sensitive. As such, it is not subject to the protocols listed below, because we don’t control it; you do. Additionally, voluntarily publicizing such information means that you lose any privacy rights you might normally have with regards to that information. It may also increase your chances of receiving unwanted communications, like spam.

**RIGHTS TO OPT IN/OPT OUT**

You have the right to “opt in” and/or “opt out” of certain of our uses of your Personal Information.  For example, you may have the opportunity to elect whether you would like to receive correspondence from us.  You will have the opportunity to opt out of Mzinga’s promotional e-mail by client the “opt out” or “unsubscribe” link in the email you receive or clicking on [Our Unsubscribe Link](http://www2.mzinga.com/unsubscribe/u/5212). You can also request this by sending an email to [privacy@mzinga.com](mailto:privacy@mzinga.com), specifying whether: i) you would like to opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from Mzinga in general, or just via-email, postal mail and/or by phone, and or/whether ii) you would only like to opt out of a certain of Mzinga’s correspondence.

Please understand that if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications from us.

**HOW WE USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

  * To allow you to register and to administer and process the registration
  * To communicate with you about our products, services and related issues
  * To evaluate the quality of our products and services, and to enhance your experience on our web sites
  * To maintain and administer our web sites and comply with our legal or internal obligations and policies
  * To transfer information to others as described in this policy or to satisfy our legal, regulatory, compliance, or auditing requirements

We may disclose personal data you provide to our affiliates and partners and to consultants, service providers, and contractors that we use to support our business and operations (e.g., delivery services, financial institutions, fulfillment services, technical support, advertising, public relations, media and marketing services, legal services, call-in centers, e-commerce and other web-related services such as web hosting and web monitoring services, and event-related services such as online and offline data capture services) who have agreed to keep the information confidential and use it only to provide the applicable service(s).

We may also disclose personal data to third parties (including without limitation, governmental agencies) if required to do so by law, regulation, or court order; to respond to governmental and/or law enforcement requests; to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with our (or others’) rights or property; to support any claim, defense, or declaration in a case or before any jurisdictional and/or administrative authority, arbitration, or mediation panel; or in connection with disciplinary actions/investigations.

We may disclose and/or transfer Personal Information to a third party in connection with a merger, acquisition, or sale.  We will try to notify you of any changed in ownership or sale by either posting it on our site or by emailing you (at the email address in the system).

If you are a registered user of Mzinga and have supplied your email address, we may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on. If we do send you information that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with a way to request that you don’t get any similar notices (opt-out).

Notice will be provided in clear and conspicuous language when you are first asked to provide us with personal information, or as soon as practicable thereafter, and we’ll notify you before we use the information for something other than the purpose for which it was originally collected. If anything in this policy seems unclear, please don’t hesitate to contact us at [privacy@mzinga.com](mailto:privacy@mzinga.com), so we can address your question and possibly clarify this document.

**SECURITY**

Mzinga takes appropriate steps to protect personal data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, or destruction, whether in transmission or storage, using commercially reasonable and industry-standard safeguards.

All such electronic information is stored on restricted database servers. We only disclose such information to our employees, contractors or partners that a) need to know that information in order to process it for us or to provide other services, and b) have agreed not to disclose it to others.

Please keep in mind, however, there is no such thing as perfect security.  Although we are committed to protecting your personal information, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communication vehicle, Mzinga cannot guarantee or warrant information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.

**PRIVACY OF MINORS**

We do not intentionally gather personal information about visitors who are under 13 years of age.  If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a visitor under the age of thirteen on our Website, we will delete the information from our records.

** ** **ACCESS AND CORRECTION RIGHTS**

You retain the right to submit and correct your Personal Information by contacting your organization or Mzinga at [privacy@mzinga.com](mailto:privacy@mzinga.com)

**PRIVACY SHIELD OVERVIEW**

Mzinga complies with the principles of the E.U.-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. Mzinga has self-certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield principals.  If there is any conflict between the terms in the privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principals, the Privacy Shield principals shall govern.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit:  [_www.privacyshield.gov_](http://www.privacyshield.gov/)

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Mzinga commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information.  Any data subject who has a complaint about the processing of his/her Personal data should first contact Mzinga’s at [privacy@mzinga.com](mailto:privacy@mzinga.com)  Written inquiries may be sent to: Mzinga, Inc,  10 Burlington, Mall Rd, Suite 111, Burlington, MA 01803, USA and Attention: Privacy Policy.

Mzinga has further committed to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy shield complaints.  If you do not receive timely acknowledgement of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfactions, please contact the EU DPAs for more information or to file a complaint.  The services of ER DPAs are provided at no cost to you.

Mzinga is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

It is also possible, under certain conditions, to invoke binding arbitration.  Please visit the Privacy Shield website for additional information.

In the context of an onward transfer, a Privacy Shield organization has responsibility for the processing of personal information it receives under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third part acting as an agent on its behalf.  Mzinga, Inc. shall remain liable under the Principles if its agent processes such personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless the organization proves that it is not responsible for the event diving rise to the damage.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our online information practices.  If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will include a new effective date, and will be posted on this page.

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like to review, delete, or updated information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us as at [privacy@mzinga.com](mailto:privacy@mzinga.com)  Written inquiries may be sent to: Mzinga, Inc,  10 Burlington, Mall Rd, Suite 111, Burlington, MA 01803, USA and Attention: Privacy Policy

Last updated: February 20, 2018
